http://www.quicktopic.com/useterms.shtml#privacy

Policies and usage procedures
Privacy Policy
TERMS OF USE
Internicity Inc. ("Internicity") provides the QuickTopicSM
World Wide Web site ("QuickTopicSM") for your educational and informational purposes. Your access to and use of QuickTopic is subject to the following terms and
conditions and all applicable laws. By accessing and using
QuickTopic, you accept, without
limitation or qualification, these Terms of Use.
1. CONDUCT.
You agree to access and use QuickTopicSM only for
lawful purposes. You are solely responsible for the knowledge of and
adherence to any and all laws, statutes, rules and regulations
pertaining to your use of QuickTopic.
By accessing QuickTopic you agree that you
will not: (i) post or use QuickTopic to commit a
criminal offense or to encourage conduct that would constitute a
criminal offense or give rise to a civil liability, or otherwise
violate any local, state, Federal or international law or
regulation, including, but not limited to, export control laws and
regulations; (ii) post or transmit any unlawful, threatening,
libelous, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, pornographic,
profane, or otherwise objectionable Content; (iii) alter, damage or
delete any Content or other communications that are not your own
Content or to otherwise interfere with the ability of others to
access QuickTopic; (iv) disrupt the normal flow of
communication in any QuickTopic discussion thread; (v) claim a relationship
with or to speak for any business, association, institution or other
organization for which you are not authorized to claim such a
relationship; or (vi) post or transmit any unsolicited advertising,
promotional materials, or other forms of solicitation to other
users.
2. TERMINATION.
The only right with
respect to dissatisfaction with any policies, guidelines, or
practices of Internicity in operating QuickTopicSM or
any Content, is for you to discontinue accessing
QuickTopic. Internicity, in its sole discretion, may
terminate or temporarily suspend your access to all or any part of
QuickTopic, without notice, for conduct that
Internicity believes is a violation of this Agreement or any policies
or guidelines posted by Internicity, or for other conduct which
Internicity, in its sole discretion, believes is harmful to other
users. Internicity may discontinue operating
QuickTopic and terminate this Agreement without
notice at any time for any reason in its sole
discretion.
3. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY.
INTERNICITY IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY INFORMATION OR CONTENT
CONTAINED WITHIN ITS DISCUSSION THREADS AND MAKES NO
REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED
IN DISCUSSION THREADS FOR ANY PURPOSE OR
ABOUT ITS LEGITIMACY, LEGALITY, VALIDITY, ACCURACY, CORRECTNESS,
RELIABILITY, QUALITY, STABILITY, COMPLETENESS OR CURRENTNESS. ALL
SUCH INFORMATION IS SOLELY PROVIDED BY OTHER USERS OF
QUICK TOPICSM.
YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF
QUICK TOPIC IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. NEITHER
INTERNICITY, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AFFILIATES OR AGENTS
WARRANT THAT QUICK TOPIC WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR
ERROR-FREE; NOR DO THEY MAKE ANY WARRANTY AS TO THE RESULTS THAT MAY
BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF QUICK TOPIC OR AS TO THE
ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR CONTENT OF
QUICK TOPIC.
QUICK TOPIC
IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS," "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS WITHOUT
REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND
NON-INFRINGEMENT.
IN NO EVENT WILL INTERNICITY OR ITS
DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AFFILIATES OR AGENTS BE LIABLE TO
YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (EVEN IF INTERNICITY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE
POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF OR
INABILITY TO USE QUICK TOPIC, INCLUDING WITHOUT
LIMITATION, LOSS OF REVENUE OR ANTICIPATED PROFITS, LOSS OF
GOODWILL, LOST BUSINESS, LOST DATA, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION,
OR ANY AND ALL OTHER DAMAGES OR LOSSES THAT RESULT FROM MISTAKES,
OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, DELETIONS OF FILES, ERRORS, DEFECTS,
VIRUSES, DELAYS IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, OR ANY FAILURE OF
PERFORMANCE, WHETHER OR NOT LIMITED TO ACTS OF GOD, COMMUNICATIONS
FAILURE, THEFT, DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO INTERNICITY'S
RECORDS, PROGRAMS, OR SERVICES. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE
EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL
DAMAGES, IN SUCH STATES INTERNICITY'S LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE
GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED.
4. LINKS.
Some links on QuickTopicSM may lead to
sites posted by independent site owners. Internicity does not review
independent sites or control their content, and merely provides
these links to visitors for their convenience. These links are not
an endorsement of products, services, or information provided by
such sites. Further, the inclusion of these links to other sites
does not imply that the other sites have given permission for
inclusion of these links, or that there is any relationship between
Internicity and the linked sites. Internicity is an independent
operating company and reference to other companies do not imply any
partnership, joint venture, or other legal connection where
Internicity would be responsible for the actions of their respective
owners.
Internicity encourages interested parties to create
links to QuickTopic's homepage using Internicity's
logos in accordance with the terms and conditions of the Logo
Policy.
5. PRIVACY POLICY.
To all users of QuickTopicSM, InternicitySM provides the following privacy
protections:
QuickTopic will inform users about its use
of personally identifiable information collected at its Web site.
QuickTopic's purposes for collection of personal information
could include billing, provision of customer service, network
management, customer surveys, subscriptions, provision of offers of
related services and other exchanges of information at its Web
site.
QuickTopic will not disclose or share personally
identifiable information collected at its Web sites with any other
companies or organizations without the informed consent of the
consumer providing the information (except as required by law or
pursuant to a governmental request).
Additionally, see the Partner Sites section below.
QuickTopic will use
information received in e-mail from customers and other individuals
only for purposes reasonably related to the subject matter of the
communication.
QuickTopic will not use personally identifiable information about the usage patterns of its
users except for internal provision of customized and enhanced services.
Additionally, see the Partner Sites section below.
IP Address
The IP Address from which you post a message (via the web form
or via email), if available, is made available to be visible to the
topic administrator, for the purpose of allowing the
topic administrator to disallow
further posts from that IP Address at the topic administrator's
discretion. (The topic administrator is by default the person
who created the discussion thread, but administration of a topic
can be transferred to or shared with other users.)
The said IP Address can potentially be used to identify the
computer from which you posted a message.
Contacting topic administrator by email
A facility is provided for
contacting the topic administrator by email, using a web-based
form linked at the bottom of the topic page via the link
with the text "Contact Us". The topic administrator's email
address is not revealed to readers, but readers are able to
send email to the topic administrator using this form. In
order to reply to email received via this facility, the
topic administrator can use his or her own email facilities;
Quick Topic does not provide a reply facility.
Cookies
Cookies are files that are sent from our site to your browser,
which your browser can then store on your disk.
On subsequent visits to the same site, your browser can send these
files back to us. They're generally
used to store information between visits to a specific site.
If you register and sign in to QuickTopic, QuickTopic uses cookies
to store your session ID which maintains your signed-in session.
If you opt to receive email for posts to topics, QuickTopic stores
your email address in a cookie so that you can easily opt out of
this by unsubscribing.
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.
Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.info.
Partner sites
QuickTopic uses Google AdSense. For information about how Google uses information from QuickTopic, visit the following link:
How Google uses information from sites that use its services.
Also see...
Electronic Frontier
Foundation - a civil liberties organization working to protect your
rights online.
Electronic Privacy
Information Center - established to focus public attention on emerging
civil liberties issues relating to the National Information
Infrastructure.
Consumer Privacy Page - from the Center for Democracy and Technology (CDT).
The EPIC
Cookies Page - definitions, links, and news.
How to
Protect Your
Privacy - information from the Federal Trade Commission.
[Note: We have a separate page, not part of this policy statement, that discusses the privacy of QuickTopic's forums.]
6. SERVICE MARK NOTICE.
InternicitySM, QuickTopicSM, Quick TopicSM, QuickThreadSM and the QuickTopic logo are trademarks or service marks of Internicity Inc. All other trademarks,
service marks, and logos used on QuickTopic are the
trademarks, service marks, and logos of their respective
owners.
7. GENERAL.
By using
QuickTopicSM, you agree to the above stated terms of
use. This Agreement is entered into in the Commonwealth of Massachusetts
and shall be construed in accordance with the laws of Massachusetts,
exclusive of its choice of law rules. Each party to this Agreement
submits to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal
courts having jurisdiction in the County of Middlesex in the
Commonwealth of Massachusetts, and waives any jurisdictional, venue, or
inconvenient forum objections to such courts. In any action to
enforce this Agreement, the prevailing party will be entitled to
costs and attorney fees. In the event that any provisions of this
Agreement are held to be unenforceable, such provisions shall be
limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that this
Agreement shall otherwise remain in full force and effect. This
Agreement constitutes the entire understanding between the parties
pertaining to the subject matter hereof, and any prior written or
oral agreements between the parties are expressly canceled.
Internicity may modify the terms of this Agreement by posting notice
of such modifications on this page before the modification takes
effect. You are bound by such revisions and should periodically
visit this page to review the current Terms of
Use.
End of Terms of Use
[For your convenience, if you wish to be notified of changes to
this page,
contact us, and we'll send notice to
your email address the next time we make such a change.
Because we can't guarantee that you will receive this mail, however,
you should still periodically visit this page.]
Copyright ©1999-2014 Internicity Inc. All rights reserved.
FAQs Contact DMCA Acknowledgements
By using QuickTopic, you agree to our terms of use. We value your privacy: Privacy statement.
